[
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Name the AWS service that checks security groups for rules that allow unrestricted access to a resource, which increases opportunities for malicious activity like hacking and denial of service?",
    "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service is used to create, store, and renew public and private SSL/TLS Certificates, as well as provide encryption of data in transit and at rest by using a protocol such as TLS?",
    "answer": "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM).",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Which AWS service tests the network accessibility of EC2 instances and the security state of the applications that run on those instances?",
    "answer": "AWS Inspector.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True / False: A Subnet can span Availability Zones.",
    "answer": "False. A Subnet must reside entirely within one Availability Zone.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What resource is a fast and scalable data warehouse that gives you the ability to analyse real-time data?",
    "answer": "AWS RedShift.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True / False: Accounts in Organizational Units can be provisioned access through user, group, and role permissions.",
    "answer": "True.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Name the service that allows you to: Access compliance reports on demand; review, accept, and manage agreements in AWS.",
    "answer": "AWS Compliance.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Name the service that protects against DDoS attacks from the public internet.",
    "answer": "AWS Shield.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Name a serverless key-value database service.",
    "answer": "DynamoDB.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Would complex read/write/change operations favor using Elastic Block Storage or Amazon S3?",
    "answer": "EBS, since only the pieces that change would get updated, and the rest of the file could remain unchanged.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What AWS Cloud Adoption Framework perspective deals with the protection of data, applications, and resources, dealing with topics like access management, threat detection, and data protection?",
    "answer": "Security.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What credential components are required to gain programmatic access to an AWS account?",
    "answer": "An Access Key ID, and a Secret Access Key.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "True / False: AWS Config is a service that provides a detailed view of AWS resource configurations in your AWS account.",
    "answer": "True.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What AWS Pricing Model offers lower prices on Compute and Machine Learning across any AWS Region?",
    "answer": "Savings Plan.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "How many Availability Zones does a Region consist of?",
    "answer": "At least 3",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What is the minimum AWS Support Plan that is required for 24/7 access to enhanced Technical Support?",
    "answer": "The AWS BUSINESS Support Plan.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What tool can be used to help AWS customers identify ways to improve workloads, including aligning with best practices, becoming more cost-effective, and becoming more reliable?",
    "answer": "AWS Well-Architected Tool.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "True / False: When an EC2 Instance is stopped, billing for that instance stops, but any attached EBS Storage continues to be billed.",
    "answer": "True.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Would static storage w/ few changes favor EBS or S3?",
    "answer": "S3 Object Storage.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which AWS service identifies security groups that allows unrestricted access to a user's AWS resources?",
    "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service is a fully managed AWS data security and data privacy service that uses ML to discover, monitor, and protect your sensitive data in AWS, particularly S3?",
    "answer": "Amazon Macie.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A _____ is a virtual firewall that controls traffic to and from AWS resources, and it is configured at the instance level.",
    "answer": "Security Group.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "True / False: In AWS Organizations, you Ccannot apply service control policies to the organization root.",
    "answer": "False. In AWS Organizations, you CAN apply Service Control Policies to the following: organization root; an individual member's account; an entire Organization Unit (OU).",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which perspective of the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework makes sure that your cloud services meet your business needs?",
    "answer": "Operations.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True or False: When you modify a file in block storage, only the pieces that changed are updated.",
    "answer": "True. But when a file in object storage is modified, the entire object is updated.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What Amazon Storage service is great for hosting static web files, music videos, music files, etc.?",
    "answer": "S3 (Simple Storage Service).",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What Amazon ML service provides language translation?",
    "answer": "Amazon Translate.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "True or False: AWS Secrets Manager enables encryption of CloudTrail data.",
    "answer": "False. Secrets Manager helps encrypt, store, and retrieve credentials for your databases and other services, but it does not help with encryption of CloudTrail data.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "A user needs to automatically discover, classify, and protect sensitive data stored in Amazon S3. Which service should they use?",
    "answer": "Amazon Macie.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What tool is used to mount a shared file system, but NOT an operating system?",
    "answer": "Elastic File System.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What service provides a target in VPC route tables for internet-routable traffic?",
    "answer": "An Internet Gateway.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Which service can be used to backup on-prem storage of virtual machines and storage gateway volumes, providing a centralized console to automate and manage backups across AWS compute, database, and storage services?",
    "answer": "AWS Backup.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which services can be used to deploy applications on AWS?",
    "answer": "AWS ElasticBeanstalk.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What AWS service protects against DDoS attacks?",
    "answer": "AWS Shield.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What perspective of the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework deals with guidance about operational risk management, to lower your overall risk profile?",
    "answer": "Governance. This perspective helps you lower risks related to infrastructure operation and failure, and of avoiding unnecessary business expenses.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which AWS service helps users to collect, process, and analyze real-time streaming data from sources including operating logs, financial transactions, and social media feeds?",
    "answer": "Amazon Kinesis.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which controls or features are shared controls according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
    "answer": "1) Patch Management (AWS will patch and fix flaws within the infrastructure, and the customer must patch their guest OS and applications; 2) Configuration management (same deal as #1)",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A company wants assistance and guidance with the initial design and deployment of services on AWS. What 2 services should they use for help with that?",
    "answer": "AWS Marketplace; AWS Partners.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What is required to enable internet access for instances in a Public Subnet?",
    "answer": "Configure a Route Table with a 0.0.0.0/0 CIDR block on the Internet Gateway.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which perspective of the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework connects technology and business?",
    "answer": "People.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A user must encrypt data that is received, stored, and managed by AWS CloudTrail. Which service provides this capability?",
    "answer": "AWS Key Management Service enables server-side encryption of CloudTrail data.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "True / False: By default, Virtual Public Clouds are configured with internet connectivity.",
    "answer": "False. When you create a new VPC, you need to enable internet access for all or part of the VPC.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A company does not own a physical data center but needs a network solution that connects employee laptops directly to the AWS cloud. Which service will meet this requirement?",
    "answer": "Client VPN. This is a managed client-based VPN service that gives you ability to securely access your AWS resources and the resources in your on-prem network, through an OpenVPN-based VPN client.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What connects a Virtual Public Cloud (VPC) to the public internet?",
    "answer": "An Internet Gateway",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which AWS service or feature can be used to block network access to a specific port on an EC2 instance?",
    "answer": "Network Access Control List (of the subnet).",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What EC2 instance would be best suited for Batch Processing jobs?",
    "answer": "A Compute instance.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 4,
    "question": "Is a Network Access List for a Subnet STATEFUL or STATELESS?",
    "answer": "Stateless. Also, by default all inbound and outbound traffic is allowed. The NACL explicitly blocks all traffic that does not meet any rules.",
    "last_seen": 739388
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What AWS service is a \"lift and shift\" solution, enabling migration of any physical servers as well as databases and applications to an Amazon EC2 instance?",
    "answer": "AWS Application Migration Service.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Which service helps users meet contractual and regulatory compliance requirements for data security by using dedicated hardware appliances within the cloud?",
    "answer": "AWS Cloud Hardware Security Module (HSM) helps you comply with corporate, contractual, and regulatory compliance requirements for data security by using dedicate hardware to store secure data.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service stores and manages configuration data, including passwords, DB strings, and sensitive information?",
    "answer": "AWS Systems Manager Parameter Store.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True / False: Amazon Inspector is an automated security and compliance assessment service in AWS that can perform classification of data in S3 buckets.",
    "answer": "False. While it is an automated security and compliance assessment service, Amazon Inspector does not perform data classification in S3 or automatic discovery.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A company needs to deploy an Amazon EC2 instance and attach a storage mount for the operating system and application files. Which AWS service will meet these requirements?",
    "answer": "Elastic Block Storage. You can use AWS EBS to mount operating systems and applications.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which service is a highly scalable DNS web service?",
    "answer": "Route 53.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True or False: An AWS Elastic Load Balancer can route traffic to different targets across different regions.",
    "answer": "False: An Elastic Load Balancer can only distribute traffic to instances and resources within a single region, but across Availability Zones.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "A cloud practitioner needs to recommend a data visualization tool for analysts to create user-friendly business intelligence insights. What service should the cloud practitioner recommend?",
    "answer": "Amazon QuickSight",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Each department within a company has its own independent AWS account and its own payment method. The company needs to centralize departmental governance and consolidate payments. How can the company achieve these objectives by using AWS services or features?",
    "answer": "Create an organization in AWS Organizations with all features enabled in one account. Invite all accounts to join the organization.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 4,
    "question": "What EC2 Plan is good for hourly spend committment for an EC2 family and region, for a 1- or 3-year term?",
    "answer": "EC2 Instance Savings Plan",
    "last_seen": 739388
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "A company wants to quickly deploy duplicate infrastructure in a different AWS Region to create global redundancy. Which AWS service will meet this requirement?",
    "answer": "AWS CloudFormation enables you to reuse resource provisioning templates to spin up resources in multiple AZs and Regions.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What service is an omnichannel cloud contact center to help you provide customer service at a lower cost?",
    "answer": "Amazon Connect.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A company wants to create a learning application for students. The application must read text out loud. What AWS ML service will fulfill this requirement?",
    "answer": "AWS Polly",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True / False: EBS stores data in multiple Availability Zones.",
    "answer": "False. Elastic Block Storage stores data in only one Availability Zone.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which AWS Cloud service should be used to run a self-managed relational database?",
    "answer": "Amazon EC2. You don't need Aurora or RDS... you can host a relational database right on an EC2 instance",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What is defined by the following: The section of a Virtual Public or Private Cloud that isolates a group of resources and sets rules for allowed network traffic. Resources in the subnet are grouped based on security or operational needs. Can be public or private.",
    "answer": "A Subnet.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What S3 classes are for archival data?",
    "answer": "S3 Glacier Storage",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What AWS service can be used to migrate data from an on-prem database to a database in AWS?",
    "answer": "AWS Database Migration Service.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What Amazon service provides centralized governance and billing for an AWS environment, including multiple accounts?",
    "answer": "AWS Organizations",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "True / False: Reserved EC2 Instances have a minimum 30 day committment.",
    "answer": "False. Reserved Instances have a minimum 1 year committment.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True or False: Relational Database Service can be implemented in Amazon Aurora.",
    "answer": "True. Amazon Aurora is an Enterprise-level Relational Database Management System.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Which AWS service gives you the ability to assess, audit, and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources?",
    "answer": "AWS Config.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "True / False: Elastic File Storage stores data across multiple Availability Zones.",
    "answer": "True.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Which AWS service provides on-demand downloads of third-party assessments of security and compliance responsibilities, and of AWS security and compliance documents?",
    "answer": "AWS Artifact.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Which service makes it easy to create and manage cryptographic keys and control their use across a wide range of AWS services?",
    "answer": "AWS Key Management Service.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Fill in the blank: Snowball Edge Storage Optimized can store ___ TB HDD or ___ TB SDD.",
    "answer": "Snowball Edge Storage Optimized can store 80 TB HDD or 1 TB SDD.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Which service gives customers the ability to audit and monitor changes in AWS resources?",
    "answer": "AWS Config.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "Name the service that is a Global Content Delivery Service, using Edge Locations to serve Cached Content.",
    "answer": "AWS CloudFront.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "What level AWS Support Plan provides ALL Trusted Advisor checks at the lowest cost to the subscriber?",
    "answer": "BUSINESS Support Plan.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS Hybrid Storage service enables a user's on-premisis applications to seamlessly use AWS Cloud storage?",
    "answer": "Storage Gateway.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which AWS service is a hardware device or virtual software appliance used for hybrid cloud storage with local caching, and without changing storage protocols or technology?",
    "answer": "Storage Gateway.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A cloud practitioner needs an Amazon EC2 instance to launch and run for 7 hours without interruption. What is the most cost-effective option for this task?",
    "answer": "On-Demand.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A company has an on-premises Linux-based server with an Oracle database that runs on it. The company wants to migrate the database server to run on an EC2 Instance. What service should the company use to complete the migration?",
    "answer": "AWS Application Migration Service",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "What AWS service scans your AWS environment for software vulnerabilities and network exposure?",
    "answer": "AWS Inspector.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS service allows users to provision infrastructure as code?",
    "answer": "CloudFormation. Enables users to spin up resources rapidly with JSON or YAML config files.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service protects web applications, and allows you to define rules that block attacks such as cross-site scripting?",
    "answer": "AWS Web Access Firewall (WAF).",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "A company needs to establish an AWS Site-to-Site VPN tunnel. Which type of gateway should the company use?",
    "answer": "Virtual Private Gateway.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "How do you access a Private Subnet securely from a corporate data center over the public internet?",
    "answer": "Connecting to the subnet's Virtual Private Gateway over VPN.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS service should be used to implement encryption in transit?",
    "answer": "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM).",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "A company is going through a compliance inspection for ISO 20017. Which AWS service or tool can the company use to download the ISO certifications?",
    "answer": "AWS Artifact. You use Artifact to download third-party assessments of AWS security and compliance postures.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "Which AWS service runs containers without the need to provision and manage Amazon EC2 instances?",
    "answer": "WFargate. Fargate is a serverless service which, with Amazon Elastic Container Service, allows you to run containers without needing to provision or manage servers.",
    "last_seen": 739390
  },
  {
    "level": 4,
    "question": "Are Security Groups STATELESS or STATEFUL?",
    "answer": "Security Groups (Network Access Control List for EC2 Instances) are STATEFUL, and by default they deny all inbound and outbound traffic.",
    "last_seen": 739388
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What architecture design principle applies to the concept of rightsizing the AWS Cloud Infrastructure?",
    "answer": "Optimize for Cost. Select the right size and type of resources running your workload by analyzing usage metrics on that workload.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS service should be used to monitor Amazon EC2 instances for CPU and network utilization?",
    "answer": "Amazon ICloudWatch. CloudWatch monitors resources and collects real-time logs. The logs can give you insight on your resource's overall health. With the CloudWatch agent installed on an EC2 instance, you can monitor your EC2 instances for CPU and network utilization.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "A company hosts an application on an Amazon EC2 instance. The EC2 instance needs to access several AWS resources, including Amazon S3 and Amazon DynamoDB. What is the MOST operationally efficient solution to delegate permissions?",
    "answer": "Create an IAM role with the required permissions. Attach the role to the EC2 instance. This will provision access to the AWS resources.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS service can help a company detect an outage of its website servers and redirect users to alternate servers?",
    "answer": "Amazon Route 53. Route 53 resolves domain names to IP addresses through records. You can also use Route 53 routing policies for failover routing to another set of resources. (This implies that Route 53 can detect when there is an outage with a resource, presumably by observing that the resource cannot be accessed over the internet).",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "A web developer is concerned that a DDoS attack could target an application. Which AWS services or features can help protect against such an attack?",
    "answer": "AWS Shield (for protection against DDoS); Amazon CloudFront (Shield Standard exists on CloudFront and Amazon Route 53).",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "A cloud practitioner is developing a disaster recovery plan and intends to replicate data between multiple geographic areas. Which component of the AWS Cloud should the company use to meet these requirements?",
    "answer": "AWS Regions. Regions are named sets of Availability Zones.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "A company has an Amazon EC2 instance that must access AWS Secreets Manager to retrieve credentials. Which identity or service is required by the EC2 instance to perform this task?",
    "answer": "IAM role. The EC2 instance will require an instance profile associated with an IAM role to be able to access Secrets Manager. The IAM role will provide the necessary permissions to the EC2 instance.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following will help a user determine if they need to request a VPC service limit increase?",
    "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor. Trusted Advisor performs many checks on your AWS environment and makes recommendations for improvement. One of these checks includes VPC service limit checks, which you can use to determine if you need a VPC service limit.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What is a benefit of moving to the AWS Cloud in terms of improving time to market?",
    "answer": "Increased business agility.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "True / False: Providing Awareness Training is the responsibility only of AWS customers.",
    "answer": "False. Providing awareness and training is a shared responsibility between the user and AWS. AWS trains their employees, and the user trains their employees.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Can IAM groups be nested within other groups?",
    "answer": "No. An IAM group can only contain users, not other groups.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "A company wants to improve its security and audit posture by limiting Amazon EC2 inbound access. What should the company use to access instances remotely instead of opening inbound SSh ports and managing SSH keys?",
    "answer": "AWS Systems Manager Session Manager. Session Manager is a node management service for the cloud or for on-premises compute units. Session Manager provides a secure connection through shell scripting. You can establish the connection without the need to open ports.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "AWS Elastic Block Store snapshots are _____ data backups.",
    "answer": "Incremental.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service gives customers the ability to audit and monitor changes in AWS resources?",
    "answer": "AWS Config.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "To reduce operational overhead use a fully _______ service.",
    "answer": "Managed.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service allows you to define and provision infrastructure resources using templates, for easy deployment of replicated Amazon EC2 instances?",
    "answer": "AWS CloudFormation.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What two services should a user take advantage of to launch a new RDS cluster?",
    "answer": "CloudFormation; Management Console.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS service helps to automate common admin tasks and perform one-time config changes at scale on EC2 instances?",
    "answer": "AWS System Manager. Remotely and securely manage the configuration of your managed instances.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which Pillar of the Well-Architected Framework focuses on the ability of a workload to CONSISTENTLY and CORRECTLY perform its intended function?",
    "answer": "Reliability.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS service provides intelligent threat detection for your AWS infrastructure and resources, and continually monitors network activity and account behavior?",
    "answer": "GuardDuty.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "Which AWS service monitors network requests for web applications?",
    "answer": "AWS Web Access Firewall.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What resource controls all inbound and outbound traffic for Amazon EC2 instances, acts as a Stateful Virtual Firewall, and by default Denies all inbound and outbound traffic?",
    "answer": "A Security Group.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service is a connection between a Virtual Public Cloud and the internet, and allows public internet traffic to access the Virtual Public Cloud?",
    "answer": "An Internet Gateway.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What AWS service is an enterprise-class relational database?",
    "answer": "Aurora.",
    "last_seen": 0
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "What is the maximum number of objects that an S3 server can store?",
    "answer": "There is no limit!",
    "last_seen": 0
  }
]